{
    "id": "a829ab6ac2dd4826a69096f3d8ebf66b",
    "title": "Sentence Correction Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Despite of having a headache, I enjoyed the movie.",
            "description": "Write despite or in spite of.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "having",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you will happen to see Jane, ask her to phone me.",
            "description": "The correct sentence is: If you happen to see Jane, ask her to phone me.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "happen",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Broadly to speaking, teachers are overworked and underpaid.",
            "description": "The correct expression is broadly speaking.",
            "answers": [
                "broadly",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Sometimes people often behave strangely when they are abroad.",
            "description": "Often and sometimes are both adverbs of frequency. Use only one of them in a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "sometimes",
                "often",
                "when",
                "Either sometimes or often"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I admit that junk food is bad for health, but I don’t think that it should be banned.",
            "description": "The conjunctions although and but mean the same. Use only one of them in a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "that",
                "but",
                "Either although or but"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Since the day was very hot therefore I didn’t go out.",
            "description": "The word since is used to give the reason and therefore is used to show the effect/result. Use only one of them in a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "very",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Because she wanted to win the first prize so she worked hard.",
            "description": "We need only one conjunction to connect two clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "Either because or so"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a man who dare to say what he thinks.",
            "description": "When dare is used as a modal auxiliary it is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "dare",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is richer than compared to ninety percent of her neighbors.",
            "description": "Richer than is enough to express this idea.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "compared to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You need not to pay for that call.",
            "description": "When need is used as a modal auxiliary, it is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t make the dish washer to work.",
            "description": "Make + object is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "the",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Most things seem to be made of from plastic these days.",
            "description": "We use made of when we identify the material used to make something.",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}